Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Detail of doors. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 10961; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1140)
  Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing
- House on Abdulrahman street. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; 10962; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1141)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Houses; Italian Writing
- A turret of a villa. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; 10963; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1142)
  Architecture; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees; Outdoors
- Entrance gates on Azzam Mosque Street. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 10964; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1143)
  Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Houses; Architecture
- Entrance of a house on Mahmoud Khater Street. 13.3 x 9 cm, 1984; 10965; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1144)
  Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Italian Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- View of no. 28 Rostom Street. 13.6 x 9 cm, 1984; 10967; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1146)
  Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Houses; Outdoors
- Group portrait. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10968; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1147)
  Boys; Men; Women; Children; Houses; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Girls; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair
- School staff group portrait. 10.1 x 15 cm, 1987; 10969; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1148)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Teachers; Color Photography; Men; Women; Facial Hair
- Group portrait. 9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; 10970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1149)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Houses; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Facial Hair; Men; Group Portraits; Girls; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group portrait of students and teachers on field trip. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated; 10971; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1150)
  Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Men; Boys; Teachers; Students; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Class photo. 10.4 x 15 cm, Undated; 10972; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1151)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Group Portraits; Women; Men; Students; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing
- Man speaking into microphone. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1999; 10973; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1152)
  Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Speeches; Men; Facial Hair
- Men addressing a crowd at a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1999; 10974; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1153)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Men; Color Photography; Audiences/Spectators; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Speeches; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Fezes/Tarbouches; Events/Occasions; Facial Hair
- The audience at a school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 10977; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1156)
  Color Photography; Medals/Insignia; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Awards; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Audiences/Spectators; Facial Hair
- A Catholic official awarding medals. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1157)
  Priests/Clergymen; Religious Crosses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Medals/Insignia; Men; Teachers; Italian Writing; Awards; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Boys; Children; Events/Occasions
- A Coptic priest awarding trophy to a student. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1158)
  Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Men; Teachers; Students; Medals/Insignia; Schools/Education; Awards; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Facial Hair; Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Men and priests presenting awards. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1160)
  Priests/Clergymen; Medals/Insignia; Color Photography; Awards; Photographic Prints; Men; Teachers; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Student in karate uniform with medal. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10982; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1161)
  Medals/Insignia; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Teachers; Sports; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Boys; Cameras; Group Portraits; Children; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Clocks/Watches; Events/Occasions
- Men and teachers at award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1164)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Awards; Ceremonies; Photographic Prints; Medals/Insignia; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Men; Teachers; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Events/Occasions; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies
- Men eating at school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10989; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1168)
  Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Food; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Events/Occasions; Furnishings
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10990; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1169)
  Religious Crosses; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Teachers
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999; 10991; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1170)
  Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair
- Award ceremony. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; 10994; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1173)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Awards; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education
- A group singing, the United Arab Republic flag hangs in the background. 8.9 x 14 cm, Crca 1958–1972; 10996; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1175)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Flags; Choirs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Singing; Microphones; Musical Instruments; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Nuns; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Pianos
- A girl performing on stage in a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; 10998; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1177)
  Nuns; Photographic Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Children; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Performance Plays; Children; Group Portraits; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers
- School event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; 10999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1178)
  Schools/Education; Boys; Nuns; Girls; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
- A young woman giving a speech at a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; 11001; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1180)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Microphones; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Speeches; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Girls; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Teachers; Performing Arts; Events/Occasions
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11002; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1181)
  Priests/Clergymen; Bow Ties; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Color Photography; Italian Writing; Men; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11003; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1182)
  Men; Teachers; Women; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Boys; Italian Writing; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Facial Hair
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11004; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1183)
  Bow Ties; Arabic Writing; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Facial Hair
- First grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11005; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1184)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Bow Ties; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Men; Women; Facial Hair
- Third grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11006; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1185)
  Students; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Women; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Children; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Facial Hair
- Third grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988; 11007; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1186)
  Head Covers/Veils; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Undated; 11008; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1187)
  Women; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Capritage swimming pool. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1984; 11009; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1188)
  Color Photography; Italian Writing; Outdoors; Swimming Pools; Palm Trees; Furnishings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings
- Group portrait of boys in bathing suits. 13.9 x 12.7 cm, 1950; 11010; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1189)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Boys; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Swimming
- Tug of war at a school event. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950; 11011; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1190)
  Men; Students; Schools/Education; Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Sports; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Audiences/Spectators
- Tug of war at a school event. 8.3 x 12.4 cm, Circa 1950; 11012; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1191)
  Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Women
- Boys saluting on top of a human pyramid in a school event. 8.4 x 12.9 cm, 1950; 11013; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1192)
  Uniforms; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Children; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
- Sack race in a school event. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Circa 1950; 11014; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1193)
  Fezes/Tarbouches; Students; Flags; Schools/Education; Boys; Hats; Sports; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Men; Events/Occasions; Group Portraits; Men
- Boys saluting at a school event. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Circa 1950; 11015; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1194)
  Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Children; Flags; Fezes/Tarbouches; Helwan, Egypt; Sports; Schools/Education; Men; Hats; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 11016; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1195)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education; Audiences/Spectators; Boys; Students; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Flags; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Boys; Crowds; Girls
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 11017; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1196)
  Schools/Education; Nuns; Boys; Audiences/Spectators; Women; Students; Children; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Events/Occasions; Girls; Women
- Students doing exercises. 8.9 x 13.2 cm, 1950; 11019; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1198)
  Teachers; Men; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Boys
- Students posing in front of Helwan Observatory. 14.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated; 11020; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1199)
  Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Students; Boys; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Observatories; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Schools/Education
- Priests and a student feeding a giraffe in Giza zoo. 9.6 x 7.5 cm, Undated; 11021; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1200)
  Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Giza, Egypt; Animals; Boys; Hats; Zoos; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Children
- Boys at the sea front in Suez. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950; 11022; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1201)
  Swimming; Boys; Group Portraits; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait on a wooden boat. 9.1 x 13.4 cm, 1950; 11023; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1202)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Nile River; Outdoors; Men; Boats/Ships; Swimming; Boys; Photographic Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Water; Transportation; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- Group portrait at the beach. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950; 11024; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1203)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Umbrellas/Parasols; Swimming; Seas; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Beaches; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Water
- Two boys at the beach. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950; 11025; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1204)
  Seas; Egypt; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Swimming; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Photographic Prints; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Water
- Two boys playing checkers/draughts. 8.8 x 14.3 cm, 1950; 11026; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1205)
  Backgammon; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Toys; Children; Animals; Dogs; Group Portraits
- Boys writing at a table. 9.1 x 14 cm, 1950; 11027; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1206)
  Men; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Suez, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Pens/Inkwells; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- A castle style building with turrets. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, Undated; 11029; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1208)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Palm Trees
- Men and boys in front of building. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated; 11030; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1209)
  Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees; Men; Buildings; Boys; Group Portraits; Hats
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Circa 1950; 11031; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1210)
  Boys; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Water; Gardens; Group Portraits; Students; Lakes; Children; Parks; Outdoors; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 5.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated; 11032; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1211)
  Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Students; Boys; Parks; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 5.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 11033; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1212)
  Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Italian Writing; Statues/Sculptures; Parks; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Water; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Schools/Education
- Group portrait on a wooden sculpture. 5.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 11034; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1213)
  Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Children; Parks; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Schools/Education
- Group portrait in the Japanese Gardens. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 11035; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1214)
  Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Teachers; Outdoors; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Gardens
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 7.2 x 12.4 cm, 1950; 11036; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1215)
  Water; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Boys; Men; Italian Writing; Students; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 14 cm, 1950; 11037; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1216)
  Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Palm Trees; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Students at Japanese Garden. 7.5 x 10.4 cm, Undated; 11038; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1217)
  Helwan, Egypt; Water; Children; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Outdoors; Boys; Group Portraits; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Students; Gardens; Water; Schools/Education; Teachers; Men
- Students and teachers holding a lamb. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Circa 1950; 11039; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1218)
  Students; Teachers; Boys; Outdoors; Men; Children; Animals; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheep; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Gardens; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Students in front of the pyramids. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950; 11040; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1219)
  Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Hats; Boys; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Giza, Egypt; Children; Italian Writing; Pyramids; Group Portraits
- Group portrait. 8.9 x 14.2 cm, Circa 1950; 11041; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1220)
  Palm Trees; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Men; Uniforms; Students; Group Portraits; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Students and man in front of Ford bus. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Circa 1950; 11042; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1221)
  Men; Buses; Students; Boys; Group Portraits; Hats; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Transportation; Children; Teachers
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; 11043; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1222)
  Students; Men; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Children
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 11044; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1223)
  Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Children
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; 11045; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1224)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Children; Priests/Clergymen
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; 11046; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1225)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Students; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Facial Hair
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950; 11047; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1226)
  Boys; Men; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Children
- Group portrait. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 1950; 11048; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1227)
  Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Students; Boys; Painted Backdrops; Children; Studio Photography; Teachers; Facial Hair
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950; 11049; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1228)
  Uniforms; Students; Group Portraits; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Children